ADNAN MISTRY

UI/UX Designer | UI Developer

+91 63538 27107



mistryadnan2000@gmail.com



Nadiad, Gujarat, India



SUMMARY

Passionate UI/UX Designer and UI Developer with 2 years of experience in crafting usercentered interfaces that are both visually appealing and highly functional, as well as crafting compelling social media images that drive engagement. I believe that good design is about more than just aesthetics; it's about solving problems, creating positive user experiences, and building brand awareness.

EDUCATION

Charotar University

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science & Engineering

2018 - 2022

SKILLS

- · Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills
- · Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- · Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously
- UI/UX Design: Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, Canva
- UI Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- MS Office
- WordPress

CERTIFICATIONS

- Workshops IOT, Machine Learning
- Participated in various technical/Nontechnical events
- · Hackathon Coding Challenge
- · Certified by NPTEL in C++ Course

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jr Developer

WeblineIndia PVT LTD, Ahmedabad 2022 - Present

- UI/UX Designing
- · Dashboard and while system UI design with accessibility
- · Design the way users interact with the interface
- Conduct usability testing to identify any usability issues
- Translate design mockups and prototypes into HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Use version control to track changes to the code.
- Wireframing and Prototyping
- · Communicate effectively with other developers
- Designer Intern

UI/UX Design Intern

Kintu Designs PVT LTD, Surat June 2021 - August 2021

- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Website UI Designing
- Team Collaboration

PROJECTS

- Dashboard UI Redesign
- Hospitality Site Website
 - Any Patient have a card to Shaw their details.
- Online Medicine Store Website
- AI/ML
 - Sign Recognition of deaf-mute people
 - Anti-Theft System